Guide to Auburn Theological Seminary Catalogs, etc. Cubb.00120
Cubberley Education Library
Auburn Theological Seminary
1863-1939
Cubberley Education Library
Cubb.00120
90 item(s) Bound together: Catalogs for 1863/64, 1866/67-1873/74, 1876/77-1877/78, 1879/80-1881/82, 1883/84, 1885/86-1887/88, 1889/90-1892/93, 1894/95-1899/1900 Separately: 1900/01-1912/13, 1915/16-1916/17 1920/21-1932/33, 1934-1939
Located in Auburn, N.Y. Founded in 1818 by the Presbyterian Synod of Geneva. Following the Great Depression moved to New York City to share Union Theological Seminary's campus.
New York (State); Theological seminaries
- Auburn Theological Seminary, 1820-1870 Semi-Centenary Address and Proceedings., 1 item(s) In addition to essays gives list of trustees and other officers, plus a list of donors and donations.
- General Catalogue of Auburn Theological Seminary, 1883; 1 item(s) Includes directory of Trustees, Treasurers, Professors, and Alumni.
- Mailing List of Men Who Have Studied at the Auburn Theological Seminary, October, 1890; 1 item(s)
- Inauguration of Henry M. Booth, D.D., as President and Professor of Practical Theology, October 10, 1893; 1 item(s)
- Addresses in Love and Honor of Rev. Henry M. Booth, D.D., LL.D. Pastor of the Presbyterian Church, Englewood, New Jersey, 1867-1891, President and Professor of Practical Theology in Auburn Theological Seminary, 1893-1899., March 20, 1899; 1 item(s)
- The Inauguration of the Rev. George Black Stewart, D.D., as President and Professor of Practical Theology., September 22, 1899; 1 item(s)
- President's Report, Treasurer's Statement, Necrologist's Report, 1905-1909; 3 item(s) 1905-1906, 1909
- The President's Annual Report and The Necrologist's Report., 1912-1931; 8 item(s) 1912-1913, 1915, 1921, 1927-1929, 1931
- Auburn Seminary Record: Alumni Number, Alumni Directory, 1905-1909; 3 item(s) 1905-1906, 1909
- Auburn Seminary Record: Commencement Addresses, 1906-1922; 4 item(s) 1906, 1912-1913, 1922
- Address Delivered at the Inauguration of Prof. Hinke and Prof. Reed, January 10, 1910; 1 item(s)
- Auburn Seminary Record: Summer School and Directories of Alumni, September 10, 1911; 1 item(s)
- The Inauguration of Harry Lathrop Reed as President, October 26, 1926; 1 item(s)
- Auburn Summer School of Theology and Religious Education, 1935; 1 item(s) Announcement for 1935